I got a wonderful family man I'm married
through my wife 28 years
you know don't clap it's treacherous
[Music]
views them are a long time you'll find
yourself getting irritated by the sense
of things I love my wife you can love
that person to death but you still go
get bothered by the most miniscule
things like last Saturday she in a
bedroom breathing
now like what are you doing right now
he's taking a ball to air in a room stop
breathing for a minute let me get some
air okay and I'm a far my regular
breathing she does this thing where
she's like she take three breaths of my
one breath and unbelievably selfish at
her we in his room we don't got no
windows no ventilation you over here
heavy breathing like we oxygen luxurious
breathing fully let me get some air
I love my wife I love my kids but I feel
like my Saturdays are being taken away
from me from my wife and my children I'm
on Saturday starts off at 3 o'clock in
the morning my wife hits me in top of
the head
wake up well baby I'm trying to sleep
I was dreaming you was dreaming you
would single with somebody
[Music]
what you heard me I was Jimmy he was
dreaming he would sleep with somebody
and I'm like how does she know and I
want to dream about other things but I
knows to be watching right I can't
control my dreams is not something I can
control and I'm saying to myself how
selfish can you be
to come into my dream this is the only
time I had of myself now I gotta be on
lookout for your dream blocking but
right
seeing my dreams try to hide behind a
bush like I wanna fear later I see you
I'm the producer this is my friend Chloe
I'm not here yes you are I see you
she'll get mad at the other day how come
you'll never you but us being together
because we be together
and I wouldn't be a dream that be a
rerun
[Applause]